# list of multiple choice seerah questions and their correct answers
seerah_questions = [
    {"question": "The Prophet Muhammad ﷺ was born in which city? \nA. Madinah \nB. Jerusalem "
                 "\nC. Makkah \nD. Ta'if", "answer": "c"},
    {"question": "The great grandfather of the Prophet ﷺ was? \nA. Hashim ibn Abd Manaf "
                 "\nB. Abdul Muttalib \nC. Abdullah ibn Abdul Muttalib \nD. Abu Talib", "answer": "a"},
    {"question": "In which month did the attack during 'Aam al-Fil (Year of the Elephant) take place? "
                 "\nA. Ramadan \nB. Muharram \nC. Dhul Hijjah \nD. Sha'ban", "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "In which month was the Prophet Muhammed ﷺ born? \nA. Safar \nB. Rabi al-Awwal \nC. Rajab "
                 "\nD. Ramadan", "answer": "b"},
    {"question": "What was the name of the first freed slave to embrace Islam? \nA. Zayd bin Harithah "
                 "\nB. Bilal ibn Rabah al-Habashi \nC. Zayd ibn Thaabit \nD. Zayd ibn Arqam", "answer": "a"}]

# list of multiple choice questions on quran and their correct answers
quran_questions = [{"question": "The applied meaning of tajweed is ... \nA. Articulating each "
                                "letter from its place of articulation and giving it its due right only "
                                "\nB. Articulating each letter from its place of articulation and giving it "
                                "its due right and characteristics. \nC. Articulating each letter from its"
                                " place of articulation only \nD. Giving each letter its due right and"
                                " characteristics", "answer": "b"},
                   {"question": "Tajweed linguistically means \nA. To make \nB. To guide \nC. To make better "
                                "\nD. None of the above", "answer": "c"},
                   {"question": "How many suwar(chapters) are in the Holy Qur'an? \nA. 30 \nB. 114 \nC. 139 \nD. 124",
                    "answer": "b"},
                   {"question": "What is the longest chapter of the Holy Qur'an? \nA. Surah Ali-Imran "
                                "\nB. Surah An-Nisa \nC. Surah Al-Maidah \nD. Surah Al-Baqarah", "answer": "d"},
                   {"question": "What is the only month mentioned in the Holy Qur'an? \nA. Rajjab \nB. Ramadhan "
                                "\nC. Muharram \nD. Dzul Hijjah", "answer": "b"}]

# list of fiqh questions and their correct answers
fiqh_questions = [{"question": "The Prophet (ﷺ) said, “Verily, between a person and shirk and kufr is _____ "
                               "\nA. Praying after the time is due \nB. Abandoning the prayer "
                               "\nC. Not praying Fajir \nD. None", "answer": "b"},
                  {"question": "A prayer offered before its time has begun is not valid. \nA. True \nB. False "
                               "\nC. Maybe \nD. Not sure", "answer": "a"},
                  {"question": "When performing Tayammum, how many times do we place our hands on ground? "
                               "\nA. 1 \nB. 2 \nC. 3 \nD. 4", "answer": "a"},
                  {"question": "The first practical pillar of salah is standing(QIYAM) when you are able to do so. "
                               "\nA. True \nB. False \nC. Maybe \nD. Not sure", "answer": "a"},
                  {"question": "What is the name of the prayer for guidance? \nA. Salat al-Awwabin "
                               "\nB. Salat ad-Duha \nC. Salat al-Ishraq \nD. Salatul Istikharah", "answer": "d"}]

# general questions is a combination multiple choice questions from all subjects
general_questions = fiqh_questions + seerah_questions + quran_questions
